麦琪:这里是麦琪?马隆在进行独家专访.
Maggie: This is Maggie Malone, with this live exclusive.
进行了三个星期的长岛环卫工人罢工就要结束了.
The end of the three week old Long Island garbage strike may be at hand.
我们已经独家了解到环卫工人本地的领袖哈里斯普瑞克雷斯正在长岛垃圾大王雷吉?
We have learned exclusively that the head of the sanitation workers local,
科恩的家里,
Harry Spreckles, is meeting in secret session at the home of Long Island
牙买加海湾镇的家里秘密会谈.
garbage Tsar, Reg Cohen, at his Jamaica Bay town house.
我们不清楚谈话的实质,也不知道什么时候要结束,
We do not know the nature of their discussions, or when they will emerge,
但是我们将继续关注,让你们了解事态发展动向.
but I'll be standing by live, to let you know which way the wind is blowing.
我们现在继续19频道独家呈现的电视剧.查兹,
We now rejoin Channel nineteen's exclusive presentation of "Ishtar".
采访关于垃圾的事件时不要穿高跟鞋.
Chaz, never wear heels to cover a garbage story.
(电话铃声)喂,哦,好的,斯波洛维奇先生,我想和你谈谈.
(phone rings)Hello, oh good.Mr.Siblovich, I wanted to talk to you.
你打算让我在那儿呆多久……我知道礼服不合时宜.
How long do you expect me to be tarnded out...
I know a gown is not appropriate attire.
但是,我实在不知道会安排我去采访环卫工人罢工.
No, I frankly wasn't planning to cover a garbage strike.
他认为我穿的衣服太性感了.
He thinks I'm showing too much cleavage for a work stoppage.
斯波洛维奇先生,你能找个其他人来解放我吗?
Mr.Siblovich, isn't there someone else who could relieve me?See, I.
嗯,没有.
There isn't.
看这条路上,没什么人在看,
Well look at is this way, nobody is watching.
今晚就放吧.不,
We are running "Ishtar" tonight for crying out loud.No, I'm sorry.
我很抱歉,
I lost my head.
我头晕了.我只想今晚全身心地去领奖.
I just wanted to accept this award tonight with all my heart and soul.
但是我知道我的工作优先,不要说我对你的个人忠诚.
But I know my job comes first.Not to mention my personal loyalty to you.
不,斯波洛维奇先生,我并没有那个意思.
No, Mr.Siblovich, I'm not just saying that.Right.Goodnight.
好的,晚安,看起来我们要一起度过这晚上了.
Well, looks like we are going to be spending the night together.
查兹:这衣服很合身.
Chaz: The gown was a thoughtful touch.
麦琪:如果这不是垃圾大王的家呢?
Maggie: What if this isn't the garbage Czars house?
如果这是垃圾公爵的家呢?
What if it's the garbage Dukes?
(电话铃声)
(Phone rings)
麦琪:你好,我要去进行一次采访,你好,杰森.
Maggie: Hello.Yes I'll accept a collect call.Hi Jason.
歌手:是的,我们没有香蕉.我们今天没有香蕉.
Singers: Yes, we have no bananas.We have no bananas today.
杰森:宝贝,文艺节目快结束了,上帝保佑,你能来吗?
Jason: Honey, we are just about through with the entertainment programme.Mercifully.Look, are you going to be able to make it?
麦琪:不能.
Maggie: No.
杰森:什么?
Jason: What?
麦琪:不,我不能.
Maggie: No, I can't make it.
我得整晚待在这垃圾堆里.
I'm going to be here all night up to my cleavage in garbage.
杰森:宝贝,他们马上要喊你的名字了.
Jason: Honey, they are going to call your name soon.
麦琪:哦,宝贝,只能让你去替我领奖吧.
Maggie: Oh honey, have you're just going to have to accept the award for me.
杰森:我!宝贝,我没有资格去领年度母亲奖.至少今年不行,我不知道说什么.
Jason: Me!Honey I am not qualified to accept a Mother Of the Year award.Not this year anyway.I wouldn't know what to say.
麦琪:要说的我都写好放在你的口袋里了.
Maggie: Well that's why I left a copy of my speech in your pocket.
本:我知道他们为什么没有香蕉,他们吃光了.
Ben: I know hwy they have no bananas.They ate them all.
杰森:嘘!宝贝,我得去了,否则他们会重新考虑你的奖.
Jason: Shh!Honey, I better go, or they are going to reconsider your award.
麦琪:再见,宝贝,谢谢.
Maggie: Bye honey, Thanks.
杰森:好的,我会告诉你演讲进行的情况.再见.
Jason: Alright, I'll tell you how your speech turns out.Bye.
麦琪:再见,这就是我的年度母亲晚宴.
Maggie: Bye.So this is my working mother of the year banquet.
查兹:来点酒吗?
Chaz: Gurkin?
麦琪:谢谢你,我本来有一次很好的演讲,你想听吗?
Maggie: Thank you.I had such a good speech.You want to hear it?
查兹:嗯.
Chaz: Uh hu.
麦琪:各位职业女性们,今天来参加晚宴的路上发生了件有趣的事.
Maggie: My fellow working women.
我以为我忘了,但是后来又想起来了我的开场笑话,
A funny thing happened to me on the way to the banquet today.
我的开场笑话,
I knew I'd forgotten something.And then I remembered my opening joke.
我忘记了我的开场笑话,这就是我的开场笑话.
My opening joke.I forgot my opening joke, which is my opening joke.
看,多有趣.
See, it's funny.
查兹:嗯.
Chaz: Hu hu hu.
麦琪:说的对,那太臭了.你能指望什么呢,盖茨堡的演讲?我没有时间写演讲辞.你不知道我过去的二十四小时是多么的荒唐?你想听吗?因为我丈夫出门不在家,所以我想熬个通宵完成我的领奖演说辞.但是,并没有完成.
Maggie: You're right.It stinks.I mean what do you expect, the Gettysburg address?I don't have time to write a speech.Do you have any idea how insane the last twenty four hours of my life have been?Do you want to hear?Well see since my husband as out of town, I was going to spend all night working on my acceptance speech.But see, it just didn't turn out that way.
麦琪:迈克?西维尔,
Maggie: Michael Seaver, do you have any idea what time it is?
你知道现在几点吗?凌晨三点.
It's three o'clock in the morning.
迈克:好的,妈妈,我只是,嗯,你在干嘛呢?
Mike: Well mum.I was just, uh, uh, what the heck are you doing?
麦琪:我要跳起来,用屁股着地,发出扫地的声音,你说我在干什么呢?
Maggie: I'm bouncing my but on the bumper and making broom broom noises.What does it look like?
迈克:你在想爸爸,对吧?
Mike: You really miss dad, don't you?
麦琪:和你爸爸没关系,
Maggie: This has nothing to do with your father.
我只是想让克莉丝睡觉.
I'm just trying to get Chrissy to sleep.
迈克:哦,克莉丝在那儿?
Mike: Oh, is Chrissy in there?
麦琪:是的.
Maggie: Yeah.
迈克:为什么?
Mike: Why?
麦琪:我通常想带她兜兜风的,但是汽油没了.
Maggie: I usually drive her around the block, but I'm low on gas.
迈克:妈妈,现在才凌晨三点.
Mike: Mum, it is three o' clock in the morning.
麦琪:迈克,你要帮我吗?我的屁股都疼了.
Maggie: Mike, will you help out here.My bottom is getting sore.
迈克:是的,好.(汽车噪音)所以你要这样摇克莉丝吗?
Mike: Yeah.Sure.(Car noises) So you drive Chrissy around like this a lot?
麦琪:只在她感觉不稳的时候.她喜欢动.
Maggie: Only when she gets real cranky.She likes the motion.
迈克:我真希望我能带着照相机.
Mike: I kinda wish I had my camera here with me.
麦琪:你以为这很疯狂.你其实也一样,只是不是捆在汽车座上,而是旧洗衣机上.
Maggie: You thin this is crazy.With you we just strapped the car seat to the old washing machine.
迈克:等等,等等.你把我绑在一个洗衣机上?
Mike: Wait, wait, wait.You strapped me to a washing machine?
麦琪:你喜欢这样.尤其是转动时,旧洗衣机一开始转动,发出有特色的节奏,然后你就很快睡着了.
Maggie: You loved it.Especially the spin cycle.
吭哧,吭哧,宝贝,你替我一下吧,我得写我的演讲稿.
When that old machine started shaking, it
had that really distinctive rhythm that would put you out in a flash.Kachung.Kachung
Kachung.Honey, could you take over for me here so that I could go and
work on my speech
迈克:妈妈,现在是凌晨三点.
Mike: Mum, it's three in the morning.
麦琪:是的,告诉我你晚上去了哪,
Maggie: Well it's either that or tell me exactly where you've been and
干了些什么.
what you've been doing.
迈克:你去写吧.
Mike: Happy writing.
麦琪:迈克,慢点.今晚我去的宴会的路上碰到了一件有趣的事,我以为我忘了,我想起来了.我的开场玩笑.哈哈,那会杀了他们,你好,宝贝.
Maggie: Mike.Slow down.A funny thing happened to me on the way to the banquet tonight.I knew I'd forgot something, and then I remembered.My opening joke.Ha ha ha.That will kill them.Hi honey.
杰森:很高兴看到你,
Jason: Am I glad to see you.
两百个精神病学家开了三天的会,真快要把我逼疯了.
Being at a convention with two hundred psychiatrists for three days straight
宝贝?
is enough to drive anybody totally insane.Honey?
麦琪:我要睡了,我记得,后来天亮了.
Maggie: I guess I fell asleep, cos the next thing I remember, it was morning.
麦琪:再见,孩子们.
Maggie: See you kids.
本:妈妈,你去了哪儿?
Ben: Mum, where are you going?
麦琪:在事情变得一团糟之前,我得去完成我的演讲稿.
Maggie: I'm going to work to finish my speech, before things get too hectic around here.
开萝尔:但是你今天不是要去本的学校上一次当前时势课吗?
Carol: But isn't this the day you are supposed to talk to bens current
events class?
麦琪:什么?
Maggie: What?
本:妈妈,你不会忘记了吧?
Ben: Mum, you didn't forget did you?
麦琪:没有.
Maggie: Na.
老师:同学们,让我们向19频道新闻记者说声早上好,
Teacher: Class, can we all say good morning to channel nineteen news
麦琪?马隆女生.
reporter, Ms Maggie Malone.
孩子们:早上好,我是19频道新闻记者麦琪?马隆女士.
Children: Good morning channel nineteen news reporter Ms Maggie Malone.
麦琪:好吧,我们不如……
Maggie: Well ok, why don't we just...
老师:马隆女士,本的母亲,
Teacher: Ms Malone, who as you know is Bens mum,
要给我谈谈关于电视新闻的话题,请吧.
is going to tell us all about TV journalism.Go ahead.
麦琪:好的,我真的没有准备今天的演讲,
Maggie: Well I really haven't, you know, prepared a speech today,
不过你知道,今晚早上来这儿的路上发生了一件有趣的事,
but you know...a funny thing happened to me on my way here this morning,
我以为我忘了,后来我记起来了.
I knew I'd forgot something and then I remembered.My opening joke.
我的开场笑话,只是一个小笑话.
Just a little joke there.
老师:笑话!
Teacher: Joke!
麦琪:我敢说你们都有很多关于电视新闻的问题,
Maggie: Well I bet you all have a lot of questions about TV news,
开始提问题吧.
so why don't I let you ask away.Yes.
女孩:那是真的吗?大多的电视记者只会念新闻稿,
Girl: Isn't it true,
而没有真正的新闻从业经历吗?
most TV reporters are vamping news readers with no real journalism
credentials
麦琪:不,不是这样,那样没意思吧?没意思.
Maggie: No.It's not.Wasn't that fun.Yes.
男孩:给我们讲一下你带着本去采访坏人们的事吧,
Boy: Tell us about the time you took Ben along with you when you did that
他们还带着枪.
story on the bad guys with the guns.
麦琪:哦,你说的是哪一次?
Maggie: Oh, what story was this?
男生:西维尔参与的那件.
Boy: See I told you Seaver was full of it.
麦琪:哦,你是说走私枪支那件.
Maggie: Oh you mean the gun smuggling story.
男孩:对的.
Boy: Yeah.
麦琪:有时候带上本和我去冒险也是一件好事.你们要知道,
Maggie: Well sometimes it's good to have Ben with me on a dangerous story.
这样他会懂得如何应付危险的局面.我还记得那些歹徒们被捕,
You know, somebody who knows how to handle themselves in a tough situation.
是因为栽倒在自己的谎言里.
And as I recall those men got caught because they were tripped up by all
是这样吗,本?
the lies they told.Wasn't that right Ben?
本:嗯,就是谎言.就是这样.
Ben: Uh, um, yeah lies.That was it.
麦琪:但是我知道,他们最终都得面对事实,
Maggie: But I know this,
我想他们会吸取教训的.
they had to face the truth eventually and I think they learned their lesson.
是吗,本?
Don't you Ben?
本:我相信他们已经吸取教训了,是的,妈妈.
Ben: I sure did think they learned their lesson.Yes mum.
麦琪:还有其他人要问吗?
Maggie: Anybody else?
开萝尔:妈妈,你怎么会在家?
Carol: Mum, what are you doing home?
麦琪:哦,我早点回来完成我的演讲稿.
Maggie: Oh I got off early so I could finish my speech.
开萝尔:很好,但是你从来也没这个时候回家.
Carol: Well, but you are never home at this hour.
麦琪:我很幸运.终于安静下来了,所以我能做些自己的事.你爸爸呢?
Maggie: Well I got lucky.Finally a moment of calm so I can make some sense tonight.Where's your father?
开萝尔:他出去理发了,因为你的颁奖晚宴.
Carol: He's out getting a haircut for your awards banquet.
麦琪:哦.
Maggie: Uh hu.
开萝尔:你们走去了,我也不想待在这.
Carol: Well not that id be up to anything with both my parents gone.
麦琪:哦,我要上楼去写.
Maggie: Uh hu.Well I'll be upstairs writing.
男人:你们好,我走对地方了吗?
Man: Hi.So this is the right house hu?
开萝尔:错了,我们走吧.
Carol: Wrong.Let's go.
麦琪:开萝尔.
Maggie: Carol.
开萝尔:妈妈,这不是约会.他只是带我去哈罗尔德吧.
Carol: Uh mum.This is not a date.He's just taking me to Harold Bar.
麦琪:你要带我的女儿去酒吧?
Maggie: So.You are taking my daughter to a bar?
开萝尔:妈妈.那不是酒吧的吧,那是一个健康吧.
Carol: Mum.Its not a bar bar.It's a health bar.
男人:那里只有玛格里塔酒.
Man: They make great celery margaritas.
麦琪:真的?
Maggie: Really?
男人:你肯定是麦琪?西维尔太太,我是罗恩?加德纳.
Man: You must be Mrs Seaver.I'm Ron Gardner.
麦琪:你好,开萝尔,解释一下吧.
Maggie: Hello.Carol, explain.
开萝尔:我是在减肥中心认识罗恩的.
Carol: Well I met Ron at the diet centre.
男人:对的,我减了20磅.
Man: That's right.Twenty pounds.
开萝尔:再见妈妈
Carol: Well, see you mum.
麦琪:开萝尔,等一下.
Maggie: Carol, stop.
男人:西维尔太太,你看起来很面熟.
Man: You know Mrs.Seaver, you look very familiar.
麦琪:也许我们一起上过学.
Maggie: Maybe we went to school together.
男人:不,你是19频道的麦琪?马隆,喔,
Man: No.You're Maggie Malone from channel nineteen.
你知道嘛,你看起来很年轻,一点也不像开萝尔的妈妈.
Wow, you know you sure don't look old enough to be Carol's mum.
麦琪:你像.
Maggie: You do.
开萝尔:妈妈.
Carol: Mum.
麦琪:罗恩,你多大了?
Maggie: Ron, how old are you?
男人:二十八.
Man: Twenty eight.
麦琪:很好,很好.开萝尔,你上个生日时多大?
Maggie: Well well well.And Carol, how old were you on your last birthday?
开萝尔:大概十七.
Carol: About seventeen.
麦琪:对不起,罗恩.开萝尔,要罗恩马上离开.
Maggie: Excuse us Ron.Carol, ask Ron to leave right now.
开萝尔:但是,妈妈,
Carol: But mum, if I do that he's going o think that you are not letting
如果那样做的话他会以为你不让我和他出去.
me go out with him.
麦琪:我就是不让你和他出去.
Maggie: I am not letting you go out with him.
开萝尔:但是,罗恩,我们还得等会.
Carol: But, Ron, we will be just one little moment.
麦琪:不,我们不会去,罗恩,你必须走了.
Maggie: No we won't Ron.Ron you will have to leave.
男人:真的?
Man: Really?
麦琪:我很抱歉,你太老了,不能和我女儿约会.
Maggie: I'm sorry but you are too old to date my daughter.
男人:哦,我明白.
Man: Oh, I see.
开萝尔:妈妈!
Carol: Mum!
男人:不,不,开萝尔.那很好,
Man: No no Carol.That's good.That's alright.I'll see you.
太好了.我要再见了,我不是说还要见她,只是一次……再见.
Well I don't mean see her exactly.It's just a...Bye.
开萝尔和麦琪:你怎么能这样?我怎么能这样?
Carol and Maggie: How could you do that?How could I do that?
开萝尔:妈妈,你在罗恩的面前一点也不给我面子.
Carol: Mum you humiliated me right in front of Ron.
麦琪:开萝尔,罗恩不应该来这儿,
Maggie: Carol Ron should never have been here in the first place.
你不能约那样的人.
You can't date men like that.
开萝尔:妈妈,我知道你在想什么.只是因为他有点秃……
Carol: Mum, I know what you are thinking.And just cos the man has a little bald spot...
麦琪:开萝尔,他不是有一点秃,他根本就是个秃子.
Maggie: Carol, the man doesn't have a little bald spot.The man is bald.
(电话铃声)
(phone rings)
开萝尔:那么你就反对他?妈妈,你很令我吃惊.
Carol: And you hold that against him?Mum I am surprised at you.
麦琪:开萝尔,罗恩二十八了,他很老了.
Maggie: Carol, Ron is twenty eight.You are seventeen.He's older.
开萝尔:总是有人要更老一点.
Carol: Well somebody has to be older.
麦琪:(回答电话)你好.
Maggie: (answers phone) Hello.
开萝尔:他是个很体贴的男人,如果你看见他你会喜欢他的.
Carol: He's a very sweet guy and you'd like him if you just met him.
麦琪:我在打电话呢.
Maggie: I'm trying to have a conversation here.
开萝尔:妈妈,如果男人不能和比她小的女人约会,那么可怜的乔治?伯恩斯要怎么做呢?
Carol: Mum, if I guy cannot date a woman who is younger than him, then what is poor George Burns going to do?Hu?
麦琪:安静,你给我安静一些.
Maggie: Quiet.I meant you be quiet.Mr.
斯波罗维奇先生,你要说些什么吗?
Siblovich, are you going to talk or what?Sir.
麦琪:斯波罗维奇打电话让我来这儿,从六点钟开始我就一直和你在这等垃圾大王.但是你知道,
Maggie: So Siblovich called me down here,
现在十点了,真不知道我的演讲进行得怎么样了.他出场了.
and since six o clock I've been waiting
for the garbage Czar with you.But you know that.It's ten o'clock.I wonder
how my terrible speech went.It figure
歌手:我们今天没有香蕉.
Singers: We have no bananas today.
女士:谢谢你们的四重唱,这是第六次也是最后一次的演唱.
Lady: Thank you ladies of the String Bean quartet for that sixth and final encore.
迈克:终于结束了,四个胖女人就这么不停地唱着.
Mike: It must really be over.Four fat ladies just sang.
开萝尔:迈克,你太刻薄了.
Carol: Mike that was very cruel.
迈克:开萝尔,你还只相当于一个饼干,和她们差远了,还不能组成一个五重唱.
Mike: Carol, you are a biscuit away from making it a quintet.
本:爸爸,你得准备好,他们要喊妈妈的名字了.
Ben: Dad, you've got to get ready.They are about to call mum's name.
杰森:哦,我的上帝!
Jason: Oh my gosh!
开萝尔:什么?
Carol: What?
杰森:这是你妈的演讲稿.它……
Jason: Well it's your mother's speech.It's uh...
本:爸爸?
Ben: Bad?
杰森:顺其自然吧,我不能说那个.
Jason: Let the record show, I didn't say that.
女士:现在,我很荣幸地介绍我们新一年的年度职业母亲奖得主,
Lady: And now, I'm very pleased to introduce our new Working Mother of
麦琪?马隆?西维尔.
the Year.Maggie Malone Seaver.
我们知道麦琪是一位19频道的新闻记者.在幕后她是一个繁忙的母亲,
As we all know Maggie is a reporter at the channel nineteen news.
有四个孩子.麦琪,到上面来,
And behind the camera she is a busy mother of four.
谈一下你是如何胜任的.你是谁?
Maggie, come on up here and tell us how you do it all.Who are you?
杰森:我来代替麦琪领奖.她不能来这儿,
Jason: I'm accepting for Maggie.She could be here.She's working.
她在工作.向职业女性们问好!
Hello fellow working mothers.
女人:嘿,伙计,你到底是谁?
Woman: Hey buddy, who the heck are you?
杰森:我是麦琪的丈夫杰森.她今晚不可能来.
Jason: I'm Maggie's husband Jason.She couldn't be here tonight.Thank you.
谢谢你,但是她让我来和大家分享一些她的想法.在这儿呢.
But she did ask me to share with you some of her thoughts.So here goes.
她今晚来出席晚宴的路上发生了一件有趣的事,她以为她忘了,
A funny thing happened to her on the way to the banquet tonight.
然后她又想起来了,这是她的开场笑话.哈,
She knew she forgot something and then she remembered, her opening joke.
哈,哈.
Ha ha ha .
小孩子:哈,哈,哈.
Kids: Ha ha ha.
本:他让我们大笑.
Ben: That man told us to laugh.
杰森:嗯,
Jason: So uh, I don't think I could possible do justice to my wife's
我以为我不可能承担我妻子的精彩演讲,
wonderful speech, so I think I'll just share with you my impression of
所以我认为我应该和你们一起分享我对我妻子的印象.
my wife.
迈克:如果这和他的西尔维斯特?斯塔隆印象一样糟糕的话,这些女人会把他撕成碎片.
Mike: If this is as bad as his Sylvester Stallone impression, these babes are going to tear him apart.
杰森:我认为最晚的那一刻是最觉能集中她的所有优点.那是我刚才外地回来,
Jason: I think it's best summed up in one moment from last night.
已经很晚了.
I had been away on a trip and it was very late...
麦琪:你好,宝贝.
Maggie: Hi honey.
杰森:哦,见到你真高兴.
Jason: Oh boy and I glad to see you.
我一直在和两百个精神病学家开会,整整两天,
Being at a convention with two hundred psychiatrists for two days straight
足够把一个人逼疯了,没完没了的疯子的事情.
is enough to drive a person totally insane.
我知道你答应等我的,宝贝,
I heard enough knock knock jokes to last a lifetime.
我必须承认,我以为你做不到.天已经很晚了,
I know you promised to wake up for me sweet heart and I have to admit,
你还在这,我真得很感动,
I didn't think you would.
我爱你……我想和你谈谈.你睡了吗?
You know it's kind of late and I sure appreciate that you did and I love
宝贝,宝贝.
you...I wanted to talk to you.Are you sleeping?Sweetheart?Sweetheart.
麦琪:宝宝,哦,宝贝,
Maggie: The baby.Oh honey, as long as you're up will you check on Chrissy?
既然你醒着,你去看一下克莉丝吧?壁橱里有很多尿布.
There's plenty of diapers in the closet.
杰森:好的,我会的,亲爱的.没问题,很高兴和你谈话.
Jason: Yeah, of course I will my dear.No problem.Nice talking to you.
收音机:现在是午夜,本地简要新闻,
Radio: It's midnight, and in local headlines those secret garbage strike
今晚垃圾大王雷吉?
talks broke off late tonight when garbage Czar Reg Cohen,
科恩和工人领袖哈里?
punched out labor leader Happy Spreckles,
斯普瑞克雷斯的秘密环卫工人罢工谈判宣告破裂,雷吉说正在考虑改变自己的称号.
who says he's considering changing his nickname.
麦琪:结束了,晚餐结束了.哦,不.
Maggie: Its over.The dinner's over.Oh no.
清洁工:你这种打扮去混顿饭吃应该没问题.
Cleaner: I'm sure in a dress like that you'll have no problem finding a meal.
麦琪:哦,不,我要去领年度职业母亲奖呢.
Maggie: Oh no, no, see I was supposed to accept the working mother of the year award tonight.
清洁工:哦,这是国际比赛吗?
Cleaner: Oh, is this an international competition?
麦琪:不,这是长岛职业妇女协会设立的.
Maggie: No, it's the Long Island Professional Woman's association.
清洁工:那么我没指望了,我住在布朗克斯.
Cleaner: Then I had no shot.I live in the Bronx.
麦琪:听起来有点傻吗?
Maggie: It does sound kind of silly doesn't it?
清洁工:不,但是我很高兴我不能赢得该奖,否则它也得变成灰尘.
Cleaner: No, but I'm glad I didn't win the award.Just another thing to dust.
清洁工:往前走吧,我不会说你.
Cleaner: Go ahead, I won't tell a soul.
麦琪:你不想要点泡菜吗?
Maggie: You wouldn't happen to want a pickle would you?
清洁工:好的,我可以早点休息.
Cleaner: Yeah, I can take my break a little earlier.
如果来些热的熏牛肉就好了.
Hot pastrami would go great with this.
麦琪:你没有这么好的运气.
Maggie: You're out of luck.
清洁工:你看起来很面熟.
Cleaner: Say, you look familiar to me.
麦琪:我是19频道新闻记者.
Maggie: I'm a reporter for the channel nineteen news.
清洁工:放的那个台?
Cleaner: My Ishtar station?
麦琪:就是我们,我是麦琪.
Maggie: That's us.I'm Maggie.
清洁工:我是凯思琳,我是一名清洁工.
Cleaner: Cathleen.I'm a cleaning woman.
麦琪:我看得出.
Maggie: I sense that.
清洁工:酪饼怎么样?
Cleaner: How's the cheesecake?
麦琪:味道有点浓.
Maggie: It's a bit warmer than I like it.
清洁工:泡菜也是,你知道,
Cleaner: Same with the pickle.
我敢说你会是年度职业母亲奖获得者.
You know, I bet you are the working mother of the year.
麦琪:你怎么知道?
Maggie: How could you tell?
清洁工:你没有时间去领奖.
Cleaner: You didn't have time to pick up the award.
麦琪:你知道,凯思琳,我真的不介意获奖.确实,这也不意味着什么.不过能不时地得到社会的认可,也是件好事.
Maggie: You know Cathleen; I didn't really care about getting the award.Exactly.And I know it doesn't mean much.It's just that it's nice to be recognized now and again.
清洁工:是的.我也得过饭店的六月月度优秀员工奖.
Cleaner: Yeah.I was the employee of the month in this hotel in June.
麦琪:真的?
Maggie: Really?
清洁工:那是在1957年.
Cleaner: Nineteen fifty seven.
麦琪:那很好.
Maggie: That's nice.
清洁工:哦,
Cleaner: Oh, you know what's nice?
你知道什么是好吗?
That day all four of my kids and my husband took me out to dinner.
我的四个孩子和我的丈夫带我出去吃晚饭.整个周末家务活一点也不让我干,
And they wouldn't let me lift a finger in the apartment the entire weekend.
那才是好.
Now that was nice.
麦琪:我也应当回家见我的丈夫和四个孩子,很高兴和你谈话,
Maggie: Well I should be getting home to my four kids and my husband.
凯思琳.
It's been nice talking to you Cathleen.
清洁工:哦,我也是.慢点,你忘了你的奖.
Cleaner: Oh, same here.Hold on, you forgot your award.
麦琪:什么?
Maggie: What?
清洁工:这儿.
Cleaner: Here.
麦琪:谢谢.
Maggie: Thanks.
清洁工:演讲,演讲.哦,不用介意.
Cleaner: Speech, speech.Oh, never mind.
麦琪:年度职业母亲.
Maggie: Working Mother of the Year.
(来自杰森的信)欢迎我最亲爱的本年度杰出母亲奖回家,我们今晚都很想你,但是不会有人超过我.
Letter from Jason) Welcome home to my favorite working mother of the year.
(爱你.猜猜我是谁?注:他们喜欢你的演讲尽管我知道我来讲并不合适.
We all missed you tonight, but no one more than me.Love, guess who.
(雷蒙,你是一个幸运的男人.麦琪:哦,真高兴,
Ps, they loved your speech even though I know I didn't do it justice.
(我赢了.00:21:51,700
Pps Ramon, you are one lucky hombre. Maggie: Oh, sure glad I won this.